{
	"24": {
		"answer_false1": "\u822a\u7a7a\u653b\u6483",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "\u6575\u8266\u8239\u63a5\u8fd1",
		"question": "\u7a7a\u6bcd\u306e\u767a\u898b\u30b2\u30fc\u30b8\u3092\u5897\u52a0\u3055\u305b\u306a\u3044\u306e\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u6d78\u6c34\u72b6\u614b\u306b\u306a\u308b",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u708e\u4e0a\u72b6\u614b\u306b\u306a\u308b",
		"id": 24
	},
	"25": {
		"answer_false1": "\u79d8\u5bc6\u6d77\u57df",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "\u8981\u585e\u6d77\u57df",
		"question": "\u81ea\u52d5\u653b\u7565\u30e2\u30fc\u30c9\u3092\u958b\u653e\u3059\u308b\u306b\u306f\uff08\uff09\u306e\u89e3\u653e\u304c\u5fc5\u8981\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u5b89\u5168\u6d77\u57df",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u5371\u967a\u6d77\u57df",
		"id": 25
	},
	"26": {
		"answer_false1": "70",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "100",
		"question": "\u8266\u8239\u306e\u30ec\u30d9\u30eb\u306e\u4e0a\u9650\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "120",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "90",
		"id": 26
	},
	"27": {
		"answer_false1": "4\u56de",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "15\u56de",
		"question": "\u6bce\u65e5\u306e\u59d4\u8a17\u3092\u3053\u306a\u305b\u308b\u56de\u6570\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u7121\u5236\u9650",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "8\u56de",
		"id": 27
	},
	"28": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8cc7\u91d1",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "\u30ad\u30e5\u30fc\u30d6",
		"question": "\u30c0\u30a4\u30e4\u3067\u8cfc\u5165\u3067\u304d\u306a\u3044\u30a2\u30a4\u30c6\u30e0\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u8266\u8239\u7d4c\u9a13\u5024",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u71c3\u6599",
		"id": 28
	},
	"15": {
		"answer_false1": "\u98a8\u4e0b",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u7121\u98a8",
		"question": "\u8266\u8f09\u6a5f\u767a\u8266\u306b\u4e00\u756a\u3044\u3044\u98a8\u5411\u304d\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u98a8\u4e0a",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u6a2a\u98a8",
		"id": 15
	},
	"16": {
		"answer_false1": "\u63a2\u77e5\u3057\u3065\u3089\u3044",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u9ad8\u3044\u5c45\u4f4f\u6027",
		"question": "\u6f5c\u6c34\u8266\u306e\u5f31\u70b9\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u4f4e\u3044\u901f\u529b",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u77ed\u3044\u822a\u7d9a\u8ddd\u96e2",
		"id": 16
	},
	"17": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8102\u80aa",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u30bf\u30f3\u30d1\u30af\u8cea",
		"question": "\u6c34\u5175\u304c\u9ea6\u98ef\u3092\u98df\u3079\u3066\u88dc\u5145\u3059\u308b\u306e\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u30d3\u30bf\u30df\u30f3B1",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u30ca\u30c8\u30ea\u30a6\u30e0",
		"id": 17
	},
	"18": {
		"answer_false1": "\u885d\u89d2\u653b\u6483",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u5bfe\u6f5c\u96fb\u63a2\u306e\u8a2d\u7f6e",
		"question": "\u8239\u9996\u30d0\u30eb\u30d6\u306e\u4f5c\u7528\u3068\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u9020\u6ce2\u62b5\u6297\u306e\u4f4e\u6e1b",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u9b5a\u96f7\u9632\u5fa1\u88c5\u7532",
		"id": 18
	},
	"19": {
		"answer_false1": "\u7740\u767a\u4fe1\u7ba1",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u5727\u529b\u611f\u77e5\u4fe1\u7ba1",
		"question": "\u300cVT\u4fe1\u7ba1\u300d\u306f\u3069\u3093\u306a\u4fe1\u7ba1\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u8fd1\u63a5\u4fe1\u7ba1",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u6642\u9650\u4fe1\u7ba1",
		"id": 19
	},
	"20": {
		"answer_false1": "\u52b9\u529b\u5c04",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u5fb9\u7532\u5f3e",
		"question": "\u8266\u306b\u547d\u4e2d\u3059\u308b\u306e\u3067\u306f\u306a\u304f\u3001\u3059\u3050\u305d\u3070\u306b\u843d\u3061\u305f\u7832\u5f3e\u3092\u4f55\u3068\u8a00\u3046\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u81f3\u8fd1\u5f3e",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u5bfe\u6f5c\u5f3e",
		"id": 20
	},
	"21": {
		"answer_false1": "\u3058\u3083\u304c\u3044\u3082",
		"type": 1,
		"answer_false3": "\u9ad8\u89d2\u7832",
		"question": "\u5bfe\u6f5c\u5175\u5668\u306f\u3069\u308c\u304b\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u5bfe\u6f5c\u7206\u5f3e",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u30e9\u30e0",
		"id": 21
	},
	"22": {
		"answer_false1": "\u901a\u5e38\u5f3e",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "\u69b4\u5f3e",
		"question": "\u8266\u7832\u306e\u7832\u5f3e\u30bf\u30a4\u30d7\u306b\u306a\u3044\u3082\u306e\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u7167\u660e\u5f3e",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u5fb9\u7532\u5f3e",
		"id": 22
	},
	"23": {
		"answer_false1": "\u6226\u95d8\u6a5f",
		"type": 2,
		"answer_false3": "\u7206\u6483\u6a5f",
		"question": "\u6d77\u57df\u30b9\u30c6\u30fc\u30b8\u306e\u5236\u7a7a\u6a29\u8a08\u7b97\u306b\u542b\u307e\u308c\u306a\u3044\u306e\u306f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u5bfe\u6f5c\u6a5f",
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"answer_false2": "\u653b\u6483\u6a5f",
		"id": 23
	},
	"all": [
		15,
		16,
		17,
		18,
		19,
		20,
		21,
		22,
		23,
		24,
		25,
		26,
		27,
		28
	]
}